Floating to the sky and roaring
Look at the sparks like rain
Let the dawn burn
to share
All walks of life from the East gather together
Brother Ye, why don’t you listen to this song before making a decision?
Why not give this opportunity to the younger generation?
Who can take the lead in dealing with dead cocoons?
You can take it back to your feet and continue the trial
Let's get started
The deceitful way of the traveler is indeed feared by everyone
Sorry, I can no longer control the search.
Not calling people to evacuate
ah
Senior Iron Fist’s strength is unfathomable
The giant cocoon he transformed into became even more unpredictable
You must not stay behind
Hengli suppression
you three
Call someone quickly
Holy Son, you, Yao Guang, owe me a favor today.
So verbose
Everyone, go quickly
leave here
so many big sisters
What are you fooling around with?
You still talk about me
Didn’t I ask you to wait for me obediently?
What are you here for?
I won't come and wait for you
My little sister is not safe
careful
Don't bother
really
Is it because the senior's Tianxuan mantra is missing?
causing tremors in the plot
I just have to give it a try
really
Hey, why is it that kid?
you know this person
Had a chance encounter
Why is it that in the entire Taixuanmen
I can't even feel the breath of my seniors
Where did it go
But Silverstone is safe
Still always angry
boy
What did you just do to that giant slip?
Did not do anything
Dare to quibble
I clearly saw you carving the Tianxuan formation pattern
What Tianxuan formation pattern?
I do not know what you're talking about
farewell to you
Little brother
Since you stepped here
I can see everything you do
What is your relationship with Senior Tianxuan?
My senior and I were just lucky enough to meet each other once
He has no intention of giving any advice
save me from danger
That's all
Then do you know where he is now?
The senior is a very capable person.
How can the younger generation take away the farewell at will?
The origin of this person is unknown
Don't be biased
Take his word for it
purple moon
You were closest to this person at the time
You say
This person is indeed not far in front of me
But he was bound by Jujie at that time
I almost managed to escape with my life
He doesn't look like he knows the magic of Tianxuan.
Okay, okay, okay
Since the apple of the Ji family’s eye has said so
you
Don't waste your time on this unknown boy.
The whereabouts of the person in this brief is the real thing.
Xingfenghuayunfei
The order of Dai Changjiao
Please, all the elders of the family, please step forward to make waves
Why don't you have a drink first?
Don't care about this anymore
What do you two elders think?
They come, the security
Anyway, maybe we haven’t seen each other for a long time.
What about this guy?
I just had a quick get-together with Mr. Ye
Still unfinished
Brother Ye, why don't you go with me to get rid of the fishy wind?
Have a few more drinks
clear up this misunderstanding
Get rid of worries
please
purple jade
Where have you been during this time?
Well, that brother
I'm about to find you
Don't come here
That kid just now risked his life to save you
You two know each other very well
How could I meet him by chance?
Not familiar at all
really
Yeah seriously
That senior Tianxuan was so powerful back then
unstoppable
Hey, come to think of it
In the past, my Holy Lord Yao Guang was defeated and returned at his hands.
6,000 years have passed
The Holy Lord of the past has long since passed away
I don’t want that crazy old man who is mysterious
But still, the years are ruthless
Always an earth-shattering figure
Return ashes to ashes
Return to the soil
But his famous Tianxuan Holy Land
All of them died in the ancient forbidden land overnight
well
This is really sad
Thinking back to King Jiang Shen and the Tianxuan Holy Land 6,000 years ago
What's the difference between being you and me today?
As the saying goes, one person can become an emperor
Thousands of people become teachers
Isn't this my fate as a monk?
Elder Jiang does not need to sigh
It has been nearly 10,000 years since the Qing Dynasty of the Demon Clan
The traces of Dao he left dissipated in thirty or thirty days.
entire
It’s time for someone from the Beidou Stars to declare himself emperor in the right way.
It's a pity that we are all old
In my opinion
Young Master Jiang is in high spirits
Quite a legacy of Emperor Hengyu
Hahaha
Elder Qi Hong is mistaken
It’s not shameful
The Haoyue brothers are resourceful
Blessing of divine entities
With the Void Emperor of the Ji family who I have heard about
Quite similar
well
We are getting older after all.
It’s inevitable to get together and reminisce about the past
The family is once again glorious
This battle of positions
In the end, it all depends on their own strength.
All present are heroes of the time
I think one day I'll be able to make a name for myself
Headmaster of a certain generation of Hua
Please give me a glass of wine from all the elders present here.
I wish you all to cultivate your wives together
Never be an enemy
Cultivate your wife together
Ah, so I’m hiding here
Hum hum
I just know how to eat and sleep
Watch me draw you a pig nose this time
Um
How old are you
Still playing this kind of trick
Is it possible that it's the same as you?
Looking lifeless every day
you let go
It’s been a few days since I’ve seen my skills improve.
Let you see how powerful this lady is.
You want to bite me again
Who asked you to bully me?
You can bite me if you can
I'll let you draw a pig's nose
snort
Then you are not allowed to hide
I said you are a dog
Why do you bite people when you see them?
You have to bully people
The last bite wasn't healed yet.
Why don't you ask your machine family to comment?
It seems that Brother Ye is taking care of my sister during this time.
Ah of course
We eat, clothe, live and travel together
Live together
Just shut up. Stop talking.
let him say
ah
Ah, I mean we've always been together
never separated
Brother, listen to my explanation
ah
Ahhh
stop
Step aside
Too bad
Brother stop
His lifelong friendship actually resonated with my body
Is he too?
good
Didn't expect it
That's the case
Then it depends on how long you can hold it under Lun Hai Yi Xiang
all the time
sea ​​fish
Unbearable
A little popular knowledge about Zhetian
this force
Could it be that my ancient holy body is fighting against the image?
Ye Fan, your physique is indeed extraordinary.
The show is about to begin
Treasure of quicksand
Common people are not guilty
The crime of having a jade is handed over
Ye Fan, wake up
I promise never to steal your baby again
you promise
ensure
ah
I held him back
Please follow the QR code of Kuaishou payment
Things don't last long