This world is so desolate
Disaster
The heart threatens to turn into dust
Escape from this prison with sores and white holes
Swallow the pain
In the depression of endless fear
I have long heard that the devil flower king is cunning
I'll never be trapped by you before I meet you in front of others
It's just a matter of taking advantage of the situation
God does it and stops it
I didn’t expect it because you were just calculating.
The sanitation guard who became my devil came here
You still have to die
Your flower spots are all dead
Don't think you can succeed like this
Haoyue can actually use sealing attribute magic
bring toxins together
And he also absorbed all these toxins
You said you were going to evolve again
What does that have to do with?
Go point me at a distance
It's doomed now
Everyone enters the Tower of Eternity
Even if you meet the king, you can still chase him here
Don't even think about posting any
Insolent mere beast
Follow the smell of the explosion to find it
I thought there would be a demon hunting group
Judging from these remaining traces
They went to the province of Jacques
Looks like our new prey is on the line
Don't die
Back off quickly
Europe Europe
I gave you the chance but you still didn’t take it.
The camp is so big
How about hunting down 100 dancing swords without being surprised?
The Yaks can only act separately
Everyone, please be careful
Quick win
In case of any accident
Use soul chains to deliver messages in time
We will meet again after completing the mission
ah
Ahhh
Not everyone can take my elixir.
Strange why it's so cold all of a sudden
you are so nervous
what happened
This is their barracks
Gotta deal with them quickly
Added storm strike
It seems that everyone is going well
The mission is almost completed, huh?
ah
What's the big commotion?
Didn't Sauron only exist in ancient times?
Why did you get so obsessed with such a thing?
He was not taught by me
Haochen’s situation has changed
First go to the agreed place to meet everyone.
head of the group head of the group
Why does the fire dragon appear here?
He seems to be at the end of his life
It's like being hunted here
That's just right
The leader said that his body was indestructible
Use him to refine elixirs
After taking it, you can gain defense power comparable to that of a giant dragon.
And look at the back of that fire dragon
That's a fire dragon that's only over 3,000 years old
He is one of the victorious fire dragons
Just absorb him
Even people who don’t know how to use fire magic at all
Can immediately use level 7 Mars defense magic
Just catch the bed bugs without any effort.
Maybe also happy
I won’t leave you a whole body yet
Oh, why don’t you commit the crime if you still don’t want to be obedient?
Who is dying
Then you can't blame me
Ha ha ha ha
Lord Barkiak
What a big bald head
Kids, no one is allowed to disturb me from now on.
Let me absorb this fire dragon
Only nine precepts remain for success
I’ll treat you to a whole fish feast
Let you eat enough at one time
Ahhh
Ah, what should I do?
What should I do
Forget it if you can’t get the fire dragon
I, Lord Yakling, am here
Even the task estimator couldn't complete it
Captain, why don't we withdraw first?
See if there are any other campsites in Jacques
Can we complete the task?
we stay
I suddenly thought of an idea
Maybe you can get the fire dragon
Can escape successfully again
Maybe we can also take care of Lord Jacques by the way.
But can it succeed?
You have to look at Sima Yi
have to say
The leader's plan is very risky
But I like it
The tone of being bullied by those little fish brats
It's finally out
Still have to be careful
It's no use. Why don't I just leave and wait until there is any movement?
Oops haha
Ha ha ha ha
The little fish boys
Listen to me
I am Lord Jacques
The most shining bald head in the world
Now I want to announce to you
From today
Our fish pond
We were punished by the Yaks
I want to do it to you
Spicy and boiled
Red, raw and cut
I want to make a big fish dinner
Reward all our tribesmen
I will also skin you
Beat your bones
And your size
No matter how big it is, you still have to break it off and squeeze out the teeth.
Come on, let’s go quickly. Hey, hey.
Yaklin always fails
I'm going to blow you to the dynamite
Then come here
fall in love
meet as planned
Now it's time for Mai to appear.
Ah fish
What a big fish
Why do you want to eat fish?
this shit this year
Ah, it’s so cool to buy
Let's go together and turn the world upside down
According to the leader's plan
There should be some movement outside at this time.
Why are you still so quiet?
what a wonderful moment
Is this the prelude to entering the Nine Realms?
Help, isn't it good for you to hit someone?
Our camp was cut off
who is it
Who deleted my camp?
ah
listen
I'm waiting for the power of the giant kiln king to declare war on you
A camp for the Yaks
From today on, it belongs to our giant kiln.
King of giant kilns
You old guy wants to take my territory and kill me.
angel blessing
Haha, brother, I’ll leave it to you next.
Oops
The show begins
Even your light is also here
It's the camp you want to drag me to.
Lord Jayak can hold back such a fireball
Wrong, it should be more than that simple
Dragon Lady Sword Master
Big fire dragon rock
This is the price you have to pay
But let me abandon you
Pain, despair
You went out of your way
Quite delicious
How about you come again?
If you don't come, let me help you.
Wait you wait first
Where is my camp?
ah
You stinky fish
I am going to kill you
Even if I die
I want to pull you too
ah
Ahhh
did not expect
Even the level 9 fire dragon was blown into a skeleton
Aha
My fire dragon
If it weren't for the leader's clever plan,
Not only can we fail to complete the task
I'm afraid I'll end up here again
Isn’t there even any slag left from the King of Giant Kiln?
The self-destruction of Lord Jacques is so terrible.
Hey hey hey, I just want to eat fungi like this
Good baby
What a baby
Oh wow, there are also magic guns for both of them.
Unexpectedly, I gained a lot this time
alright
Our job with Mr. Jacques is accomplished.
Next
Let's first look for any traces of other demon hunting groups.
The captain is about to pass through the province of Jacques.
Didn’t I say that there are many Limengtun villages in Jacques Province?
Why haven't I seen anyone for so long?
What's wrong with us
Balasya
Here comes another group of people who want to die.
Prey delivered to your door, hahaha
Favorite and follow
Chase the sail without getting lost
You guys are looking at it so carefully
You must have understood the QR code scanning process by heart.
Kill one by one in action
been separated
They are dragons
slayer
you
There is nowhere to escape
Even a six-person dare to take the lead
Stop talking nonsense and support the Demon Hunting Group?
Do you want to make the same mistake again?
Move first1112
You go and help
Then let's solve it together
Invincible
Will again