If everything is annihilated in an instant
There is a kind of catastrophe called fate between yin and yang
I am still cultivating amidst all the disturbances
The ever-changing fighting spirit of the reef has rushed into the clouds
Standing on tiptoe, I penetrate the horizon
I have already turned my tears into smoke
The flame burning in my heart is still tender
The world can't hold everything I have
No longer walking with head down
I raise my hands
Turn the green sky into a dazzling rainbow
Freedom in Dreams
I fight through the sky
This crack in the universe is an extremely tiny universe
My destiny is mine alone
Woo oh love
The Eight Ancient Clans
They are the ancient tribes you are familiar with.
Soul Clan
Soul Palace
There is also the Yan clan
The Eldar
ThunderClan, you have already lost to the OwlClan
Yaozu
Yaozu, Master, are you also
That's right
I am the abandoned son who was kicked out by my master.
Master's talent in alchemy is unmatched
Achievements and reputation unrivaled in the continent
The demon tribe actually treats you as an abandoned child
Are we blind?
The older the race,
The more you stick to the old ways
Blindly following bloodline level to divide status
The bloodline of the Pseudo Emperor is too thin
So he was abandoned by his tribe early on.
Aren't you too?
The Xiao clan is known as the abandoned bloodline
Being excluded and forgotten by other Qi tribes
Bloodline inheritance certainly has its benefits
But talent and hard work are the key to success
For example, Master
Your achievements
No one in the Yao Clan can compare to him.
And a genius like me
It is definitely the beginning of a new era for the Xiao family.
Become the next legendary
You are right.
Business mutual praise apostles
I admire you.
So this time I took the important task of bringing Xingyun brother to attend
I'll leave it to you.
I will never bring shame to Master and Master Feng.
Your Majesty, the world knows about this trip
Even if there is no Doudi bloodline
My brother Xingyun will never redeem anyone.
When I come back
Bring your girlfriend over to see it too.
What? Actually, Xue Xueer
Why
I don't think I saw Skyfire Venerable and Little Medical Fairy today.
Ahahaha
In order to completely refine the evil poison body
Xiao Yixian, under the guidance of your master
To practice Heavenly Fire
After knowing that
He threw a lot of top-grade elixirs and looted them.
I also went into seclusion.
Before you set off
They should be able to get out.
Ha ha ha ha
Break it down with me
This Dragon Spirit and Tiger Mighty Pill is really awesome!
Not only has the strength been completely restored to its previous state
Even feels a lot younger.
What what Dan
What did he feed you?
Good
Haha, Xiao Yan is here.
Come and see the deity
The true strength of this six-star Dou Zun
Skyfire Fist
You have to pay for the house you damaged.
Just fixed it a few days ago
This fighting spirit is from the Little Doctor Fairy
Seems stronger than me.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Little Doctor, is your hair
Thanks to the help of Yao Lao
The evil poisonous body has been completely refined by me
In the forehead mark
I don't have to worry anymore
It's really great
The Soul Palace did not attack Fengxian and I sat in Xinyunge
Inconvenient to leave
Next Steps
Xiao Yan's encouragement will be in the hands of a few of you.
Medicine old rest assured
Xiao Yan is too weak
We will protect him well.
Even if you give it to me, Qinglian
Swear to protect the master
Dear brothers and sisters,
Please protect me.
This is the ancient holy city.
The remains of the ancient tribe's construction
It is the only ancient ruins inhabited by humans on the continent.
Wow
Who is coming?
No one without an invitation is allowed to enter
Sitting in the barrier covering the ancient holy city
Contains the power of fighting the earth
No invitation
It's impossible to sneak into the city.
Hahaha invitation?
I have it.
How do I look now?
You can't embarrass Xu'er.
Not as handsome as me
The man on the plane seems to be Xiao Yan
Xiao Yan is here
Go and inform the commander
ah
Are they lining up to welcome me?
Ha, Xiao Yan is so impressive.
amazing
Xiao Yan, you actually dare to come and seek death
Dragon Fist
You're here at the right time.
Let's settle the old score with the scumbag today
You shave your head
How is it possible?
You are just an ant, but you bully the weak and fear the strong.
You are trash, you are worse than an ant.
Hum, bold lunatic
How dare you hum in my Gu tribe?
I'm waiting to be invited
Is this the ancient tribe's way of entertaining guests?
Why are the Black Rock Army so noisy?
Hey, who are you?
Xingyun Pavilion
Xiao Yan was invited to attend Miss Xun'er's coming-of-age ceremony.
Brother San can't let him in
Entering the ancient world, he cannot let Miss Sharp Knife
Kill him
Xiao Yan, right?
I have heard of your name.
But the Valley Clan does not welcome you to leave
No one can stop me from seeing Xuan'er
We must enter Shengcheng today
Hmm, mob
Black Eyes, take them down.
Brother Xiao Yan is mine
I wonder who dares to touch him today.
Cher
Miss Cher
This guy is not worthy of you.
Oh, that's it.
No wonder the two commanders suddenly wanted to attack the guests
This Xiao Yan seems very strong
The Seventh Commander was knocked down with one punch.
As expected, he is the one that the young lady likes.
You all shut up.
Master, is this Mrs. Shao?
Hongmei is so awesome!
Oh, that Xue'er
Of course I am you
From the inside to the outside
but but but
We can talk about this when we're alone.
How embarrassing in front of so many people
That's not what I meant.
wrong
That's exactly what I meant, but
Cher
Oh no
I haven't finished speaking yet.
I reminded you long ago
The retreat is located at such a high place
Bad signal
I wanted to help
As a result, what I just said
Instead, it will put Brother Xiao Yan in danger.
Ah, what should I do?
If you can't even stand this test
Why do you want to take the young lady from the ancient tribe?
Tiansha
Playing tricks on Xiao Yan
Surprisingly
How is it possible?
Hum, I want to move the master
Get past us first
Hehehe
Wow
Seven Stars Diamond is worthy of being the single champion
Even the bodyguards are so impressive
The ancient goddess also favored
Real life winner
Can we go into town now?
Or do we need to kill our way in?
Such a big tone
Ertouling
There are three thousand fireworks in the world
Like a touch of tenderness in your eyes
Someone is walking alone across the desert
Rushing towards this storm and thunder disaster
A thousand and one mistakes
People's hearts are in chaos and it is difficult to distinguish between friends and enemies
The red fire has not yet burned away the past, the grudges and the right and wrong
Frost and snow kissed my brows and I looked around the world and the mountains and rivers
Make a promise together
Laughing at the cause and effect to the heaven and earth
It's the legend of this world
Wasting time in my dreams
Like a passing traveler