If everything is annihilated in an instant
There is a kind of catastrophe called fate between yin and yang
I am still cultivating amidst all the disturbances
The ever-changing fighting spirit of the reef has rushed into the clouds
Standing on tiptoe, I penetrate the horizon
I have already turned my tears into smoke
The flame burning in my heart is still tender
The world can't hold everything I have
No longer walking with head down
I raise my hands
Turn the green sky into a dazzling rainbow
Freedom in Dreams
I fight through the sky
This crack in the universe is an extremely tiny universe
My destiny is mine alone
Woo oh
Now is the time when the first and second elders must die.
Guan Ziyan has had this happen again
The three kings of Wei were ambitious.
I won't miss this opportunity.
Dragon rest assured
We will definitely sacrifice our lives to protect Xiao Yan.
Who wants to stop them?
Unless you step over my Black Star's body first
I will also do my best to protect the young master
You have a more important mission, little girl.
This is the ancient dragon blood extracted from my body.
Once Xiao Yan's energy is depleted too much
Be sure to feed him in time
Remember
Don't worry, elder.
Sunrise and sunset
Around the clock
The flame never goes out
No rest and no sleep
In the blink of an eye, more than a month has passed
Elder, how long will this take?
Wait a minute
Energy crystals have been refined a lot
It should be soon.
But if you delay any further
I'm afraid Brother Xiao Yan won't be able to hold on.
Master
I can hold on a little longer.
Even if I have only one last breath left
I will never give up on the Fourth Master
I will definitely wake you up, you little bitch
Damn it! Xiao Yan is overdrawing his own essence.
This will damage the foundation.
Master, can't you take it down so fast?
Kirin girl can't go there
At this time, the temperature of the internal fire is extremely high
You're afraid the corpse won't be able to resist
And that was his realization that he had no intention of burning his life.
This is just nonsense.
How could you be here, elder?
He won't come again
I'm afraid you guys will have to collect that kid's body.
Get out of the way
Come on, come and help him.
How can there be an ancient dragon garden unique to Changtianlong?
This kind of damage will automatically downgrade the level.
For Longhua
For the Dragon Clan
What is this sacrifice?
The monster has upgraded
Zi Yan's essence is melting faster
Qianlong's Yuan Ling can upgrade the strange fire
It's too difficult. Just refine the crystal in Zi Yan's body.
You can wake him up.
Elder, I'm fine.
Don't mind me
This upgrade is only temporary.
It's up to you next.
Controlling the flame
I will never disappoint the elders.
Everyone is working hard for you
Come on Zi Yan!
Wake up
Um
Who sneaked up on me?
Get out of here!
Get out of my way, Paige
You don't have a say here.
By order of the Western Dragon King
Take the Royal Blood
Visit Xilong Island
The Southern Dragon King ordered me to come and question him.
Secretly Hiding Royal Blood
What does Donglong Island want to do?
Damn, these bastards are here.
Picked the most critical time
Hei Qing protects Xiao Yan and Zi Yan
Leave these enemies to us.
Where is the pig cage on Donglong Island?
Donglong Island identifies the Dragon King
Tang hybrids are also worthy of being king
Offending the Dragon King
His crime should be punished
Humph, stubborn
Bring your stubbornness and the Donglong Island group to destruction
Dragon Island Panlong Army
Xilong Island Dragon Armor Army
I tear them up
The generals of Donglong Island met the attack
Protect the Dragon King
I am the elder
The second elder is in retreat
Yan Rong and his shrimp soldiers and crab generals are so presumptuous
Please, please hurry up.
Coming Soon
It's almost there
Just a little bit
ah
Xiaoxian, you say
Why do I always feel a little uneasy today?
Oh, isn't this nonsense?
Your apprentice has been away for more than a month and we can't contact him.
You have a really big heart.
Has it been that long?
And who do you call Xiaoxian?
I have sent disciples to Hua Zong to inquire before.
It is said that Shao Yan left a long time ago
But it has not been seen yet
Very strange
Something's not right
This is the girl with royal blood.
Can you give him to me, handsome boy?
My disciples dare to move
Get out of my way
The breath of Halloween
It's Master Yaochen
Xiaoyan, do your thing.
Don't be distracted
yes
Half Life of Man
Why do you want to interfere in the grievances of my ancient dragon clan?
Mopping the floor is my job.
If you don't want to die, get out of here
Oops
I was almost assisted by you
If I were really here
I might still have some concerns.
How dare a mere soul illusion speak so arrogantly?
The little swallow can't be deceived
Persistence
The master will come to rescue you soon.
I'll save him.
Lion and Dragon Fight
Black Qin, it depends on you
ah
Don't touch the master
Nine Demon Emperor Hades
Human Skeleton Snake
He was just a former defeated general of Taixu Ancient Dragon.
ah
Hate
Almost
Just a little bit more
I can't let him disturb me at this time.
Emperor Demon
I want to be faster.
Ah, ten thousand yuan of blood
Strange Fire
Too late, little guy.
It's a pity that your puppet is vulnerable
Hurt his hair
Want your life
Hey Xiao Yan
Look at you, you're so silly
This breath of no blood
Awakening Dragon King Blood
ah
Who said there are three thousand fireworks in the world?
Like a touch of tenderness in your eyes
Someone is walking alone across the desert
Rushing towards this storm and fire
thousand and one mistakes
People's hearts are in chaos and it is difficult to distinguish between friends and enemies
The red fire has not yet burned away the past, the grudges and the right and wrong
Frost and snow kissed my brows, I looked up at the world and mountains and rivers
Make a promise together
Laughing at the cause and effect to the heaven and earth
You are the legend of this world
Wasting time in my dreams
Like a passing traveler