If everything is annihilated in an instant
There is a kind of catastrophe called fate between yin and yang
I am still cultivating amidst all the disturbances
The ever-changing fighting spirit of the reef has rushed into the clouds
Standing on tiptoe, I penetrate the horizon
I have already turned my tears into smoke
The flame burning in my heart is still tender
The world can't hold everything I have
No longer walking with head down
I raise my hands
Turn the green sky into a dazzling rainbow
Freedom in Dreams
I fight through the sky
This crack in the universe is an extremely tiny universe
My destiny is mine alone
Woo oh love
Friends in front, please help me.
ah
Pursuit method
There are so many black magic thunders
I made a ninth-grade pill
The pharmacist only summoned one.
Crazy little brother
Senior captures the monster
Farewell
It's not that I don't help
Sorry, my ability is really limited.
I hate it so much
Young man, you run so fast.
Seniors please
It was a close call that I almost ran out of energy.
You are just a five-star Dou Zun.
Dare to come to the Void Thunder Pool for training
If I hadn't met my senior
I will never experience such danger.
The senior must have escaped from danger.
Sorry, I can't accompany you
Goodbye haha
Young people still have a little temper
In fact, it's much safer if we form a team together
I don't need it.
Why did I come back again?
Farewell
Senior, I was wrong.
Give me a ride
Haha brat
Burning food?
Hahaha I like it
It should be safe here.
Young man
You also have the Emperor's Ancient Wing
Dragon King Bone Armor
Which ethnic group are they from?
Are you the legendary dragon and phoenix hybrid?
Purebred human
Thank you for not admitting it.
I understand, I understand
Hey Hey Young Man
You see, we are so related.
How about cooperating and breaking through the red zone?
Don't look at this black magic thunder, it's very scary
Absorbed, it is a great tonic
Thank you for not bothering me. I am old.
Hey, don't be like this.
Actually, the old man is very good.
If it wasn't for the fear of causing a riot
So that they won't chase me everywhere.
Why don't you bring them here?
I'm running around
Adjournment to the Ono brothers
Go first if you have something to do
See you later
Why
Give money, bro
I heard thunder outside.
Are you okay?
Ah, it's okay.
How come you suddenly come here?
The bamboo forest elder said he has the key for you.
Please leave with me as soon as possible.
Gone
Fortunately, the old man hid quickly
This guy's name is Xiao Yan
This name always sounds familiar to me.
It's really nice
The young man
It would be nice if there were students like this in my college.
Master, Master
Kirin hahahaha
I'm out of the customs.
Six-star Dou Zun Hehe
Hum, thanks to the dragon energy in the ancient dragon's eyes
Soul of the Ancient Serpent
I have almost completely refined it.
Who dares to bully the young master next time?
I'll blow his head off.
He is indeed the world's first prodigy
Practice makes things more effective
By the way, where is the Master?
Soon after the Master went into seclusion
The Venerable left in a hurry.
Xiao Yan, Mr. Zhang
Your master seems to have something important to do.
Leave this letter before leaving
Look at this Jianxin Express Rail
Urgent
Walking in such a hurry
Is there something wrong with Shin Yun?
No, I'm leaving now.
Brother Xiao Yan has done a great favor to the Taixu Ancient Dragon Clan
I believe that Yun-hye is really in trouble.
I'll go with you
I'll definitely be able to help
Thank you very much, Brother Heiqing
Hahaha
It's a good opportunity for people to recall the past.
My power of the ancient dragon
Thunder
You take 300 Dragon King soldiers and follow Brother Xiao to support Xingyun Pavilion
Master, wait for me
Master Daqiang
Don't be in trouble
I'm back
Hey, Senior Brother Xiao Yan
What a coincidence
Master's birthday ceremony is about to begin
The young master is back
You brought so many friends with you.
Very good
Today is Pavilion Master Feng's birthday.
Come celebrate
The guests also come to play.
This is the market.
Is it a person?
Who knows?
I guess I was tripped up by the prosperity of the world.
Let your gaze be fixed on the rolling red dust
In contrast
I'm just having a birthday
What a tiny thing.
How unworthy he is to pay attention to me
Just disappeared like before
So many years
Get used to it
Does it matter?
Is it important?
Is this angry?
Um
Very angry
Master, please don't come back.
Wow fireworks!
I remember there was a fireworks segment.
Look at your results.
You're such a jerk.
Hahaha, the banquet is about to begin.
Wow, that was a close call.
I almost didn't make it.
Master
What is the emergency situation?
I kept you outside for so long.
Finally got a real body
Of course, we should enjoy the world to our heart's content.
You wandered around everywhere, right?
But I do have something important to tell you.
Invitation to the ancient tribe's 20-year coming-of-age ceremony
Ancient tribe Xueer Xiaoyanzi
Do you know what a coming-of-age ceremony is?
Uh, I don't know
That silly boy is
Squeak, squeak, I lied to him
Hahaha
It takes 20 years to hold the first session
The coming-of-age ceremony can only encourage the best young generation
Only then can you participate
Deshuzuwen
Only the most powerful forces will be invited to attend.
If I hadn't entered the semi-saint Xin Yun brother this year
I'm afraid I won't get this invitation yet.
This snake is rare
The Ancient Eight Clans
Nowadays, only the ancient tribe still likes to make such a fuss.
Which eight tribes are the ancient eight tribes?
The Eight Ancient Clans
They are the ancient tribes you are familiar with.
Soul Clan
Soul Palace
There is also the Yan clan
Ancestral Eldar
Thunder Clan, you have already defeated the Owl Clan and the Yao Clan
Who said there are three thousand fireworks in the world?
Like a touch of tenderness in your eyes
Someone is walking alone across the desert
Rushing to this storm to resolve the confusion
Thousands of Knights and Swords by Mistake
People's hearts are in chaos and it is difficult to distinguish between friends and enemies
The red fire has not yet burned away the past, the grudges and the right and wrong
Frost and snow kissed my brows, I looked up at the world and mountains and rivers
Make a promise together
Laughing at the cause and effect to the heaven and earth
It's the legend of this world
Wasting time in my dreams
Like a passing traveler