If everything is annihilated in an instant
There is a kind of catastrophe called fate between yin and yang
I am still cultivating amidst all the disturbances
The ever-changing fighting spirit of the reef has rushed into the clouds
Standing on tiptoe, I penetrate the horizon
I have already turned my tears into smoke
The flame burning in my heart is still tender
The world can't hold everything I have
No longer walking with head down
I raise my hands
Turn the green sky into a dazzling rainbow
Freedom in Dreams
I fight through the sky
This crack in the universe is an extremely tiny universe
My destiny is mine alone
Woo oh love
This aura of dragon blood
Awakening the Dragon King Pure Blood
Dragon King
True Dragon King Pure Blood
Wake up
I, Taixu Ancient Dragon, finally got the Dragon King's Bones again
Welcome the Return of the Dragon King
This is the true pure-blooded might of the Dragon Emperor!
Emperor's Wings
Bone Dragon Body
Liu Er waits for his life
Tell that to the Three Island Sword King
Taixu Ancient Dragon Clan
Only the Dragon King
No Dragon King
A trace of royal blood in them
The Emperor will take it back personally.
Let go, Master.
Don't touch them
Master
Little Yanzi
You woke up
Master
The Battle of Dragon Island Many Years Ago
You couldn't get up after you were seriously injured while saving Zi Yan
I slept for several years many years ago
Five years
No way
500 years
500 years of changes
You were defeated by the elders of Beilong Island.
And pressed under the Five Finger Mountain
Later, the master came to save you
It's a pity that you are seriously injured.
I will only take you to the Western Continent.
Searching for the Supreme Sutra Left by the Buddha
Time Passes
All your friends and family are gone.
This comic was finished 40 years ago.
The teacher has actually passed away
Now I am just a remnant soul in front of you
Your feet are exposed.
Oh, that's an illusion.
Don't interrupt
Stop making it up. Do you really think I'm stupid?
I was in a coma for only 5 days.
How's Ziyan?
She's fine.
At the last moment, she was successfully rescued
She also dealt with the other fake kings of Dragon Island.
That's good
What's wrong with you, Xiaoyan?
I feel a power in my body
So lazy that it's about to overflow
Master,
What weird special medicine did you give me?
It's none of my business.
But this power is very powerful.
ah
Then I really have to try it.
Roar, roar, roar, roar
Don't you
Wait a minute
Don't try it here.
What happened? What happened?
12 Brother, are you okay?
Ha, sorry.
I did it
I will compensate you.
Come on, look at God.
Ah, little sage
Are you okay?
Ha ha ha ha
Congratulations to Brother Xiao Yan
This is the power of the Dragon King that I and others envy.
Ah, the power of the Dragon King
You used up all your energy before
Great damage to the foundation
Zi Yan felt distressed and guilty
I gave you a ray of the evolved Dragon King's power.
You're a blessing in disguise.
Ziyan wakes up
So where is he now?
Lord Dragon King has not yet completely absorbed the Dragon King
The Northern Yuan Dynasty forced itself to wake up and repel the enemy
I have also given you the power of the Dragon King.
I fainted at that time
Now the Dragon King is still in seclusion on the top of the volcano
Absorbing residual current energy
When the time comes
Will wake up
I want you to bring
That little girl also helped a lot this time
How is Qinglin?
This kid is so reckless.
Almost attacked by the ancient celestial snake
I sent him to the Ancient Dragon Tomb to heal his wounds.
The dragon energy is very strong there
Helps to suppress and refine the ancient sky snake
Everyone is fine
Great, thank you, Brother Heiqing.
It's too empty
The Ancient Dragon Clan should thank Brother Xiao Yan
Saving the Dragon King is saving me
Ancient Dragon Clan
This love, this hate
Never Forget
Elder, you are too polite.
I just did what I was supposed to do
Great favor cannot be repaid
It's a pity that Xiao Yan is not a dragon
Otherwise, it would be enough to be crowned the Dragon King.
Hahaha, Brother Xiao Yan and the Dragon Emperor have such a good relationship
It is completely possible to marry into the ancient dragon clan
Make him an emperor
Under the Breathing Dragon
Above the Ten Thousand Dragons
Hey, don't talk nonsense.
I always treat Zi Yan as my little sister
I can't commit a crime
The complete form after being activated by the Dragon King
It can be said to be peerless
She is the most beautiful woman in Douqi Continent.
No, I have unfinished business.
I'm still far away
Need more experience
Improve your strength
Master, please go!
Let's go to the West to obtain Buddhist scriptures.
Ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
Just
Wukong, you finally woke up
Oops, sorry anyway.
I am handsome and talented
Hua Heng Yi
But I already have someone in my heart
Being a royal family is absolutely impossible
I was just joking.
Don't take it seriously.
How can the bloodline of the Dragon Queen's descendants be mixed with foreign races?
Don't mind.
Brother Yan
Ahahahahaha
But my ancient dragon clan will repay any favor.
Dragon Island has a good place to improve your strength
It's right in front.
here it is
This is the void thunder pool of my Dragon Island
Wow
Awesome Thunder Force
I'm afraid it's stronger than the Dan Lei that Dan Hui attracted before.
This is exactly where I want to be
This thunder is extremely dangerous
Even the Taixu Ancient Dragon Clan members dare not enter lightly.
You really have to go in alone.
A sword is sharpened by grinding
It is this thunder force that is needed to temper and polish the body.
Remember to release your puppets.
Tempering and upgrading
Yes, the level of Tian Yao Kui is indeed low.
I'm almost useless in the recent battle.
Hey, I say that's enough.
Oh
Provoked a group of people
Bad luck, bad luck, bad luck
Oh, if we force it, it will cause a riot.
Oh, what a trouble.
Why
That is
Well done
Dragon King Bone Armor
People from the Taixu Ancient Dragon Clan
Friends in front, please help me.
Oops!
At least half life
What's going on?
Who said there are three thousand fireworks in the world?
Like a touch of tenderness in your eyes
Someone is walking alone across the desert
Rushing towards this storm and fire
A thousand and one mistakes
People's hearts are in chaos and it is difficult to distinguish between friends and enemies
The red fire has not yet burned away the past, the grudges and the right and wrong
Frost and snow kissed my eyebrows
See the world and mountains and rivers
Make a promise together
Laughing at the cause and effect to the heaven and earth
You are the legend of this prosperous world
Wasting time in my dreams
Like a passing traveler