Subtitle by [www.gogoanime21.eu.org], thank you for faithfully watching at "[www.gogoanime21.eu.org]"
The Hong family, one of the two major families in Tianbeicheng
Use the power of Fenglei Pavilion to force a marriage with the Han family
Accomplish the annexation plan
At the same time, the Hong family also sent people to kidnap Han Xue
In an attempt to force the Han family to compromise
Fortunately, Xiao Yan took action to disintegrate it.
Later, Xiao Yan repayed Han Xue's life-saving grace and owed his debt to his senior Han Yue.
He decided to stand up for the Han family
Accept Hong Chen’s martial arts challenge
In order to dispel the concerns of the Han family, Xiao Yan defeated Han Tian with the power of space.
Gained approval from everyone in the Han family
Xiao Yan, who is responsible for the future of the Han family
An absolute victory must be used to change the fate of the Han family.
Xiao Yan
What do you want
Have fun
Just kill me
tell me
The place where the teacher is imprisoned in the Soul Palace
Want to save that old guy
Do you really think anyone can enter the Soul Palace?
I said I said
this is your last chance
My patience is running out
I'll tell you where Yaochen is imprisoned
Just let me go
You have no right to bargain with me
stop stop
I said
The city in the western region of Zhongzhou
The Soul Palace has a branch hall there
drug dust
He was detained there
but
There is a Dou Zun-level elder sitting in that branch hall.
There are also several guardians
Could it be that the hall that my soul sensed last time
It's Hades
If so
It must have been the extremely terrifying soul power that day
It belongs to that respected elder
All I know is this
please let me go
If you can subdue three thousand flames after the elixir meeting,
It’s just that I have more confidence to rescue the teacher.
But now it’s better to recover from the injury as soon as possible
Help the Han family win the competition
elder sister
Cher
It's been three days
Why haven't you come out yet?
He had been seriously injured before
sister
Do you think Xiao Yan will be fine?
It's rare to see you care so much about someone
Cher
Could it be you
Do you like Xiao Yan?
sister
What are you talking nonsense about?
How long have I known him?
Sister, I just want to remind you
Xiao Yan is indeed outstanding
But such a man
It's hard to stay for anyone
and
He already has a girl he likes
that girl
Are you as good as him?
More than excellent
Even the top three of Canaan College
I can't even last ten rounds in her hands.
her age
Even younger than Xiao Yan
Such talent for cultivation
Almost demonic
Xiao Yan
you recovered
Time is up
Um
How is your injury?
Almost all healed
Go
Don't keep Uncle Han and the others waiting too long
Head of the Han family
You're here
I thought you were going to stop fighting today
The family respect is ruined
Since the Hong family wants to maintain ten years of peace with my Han family,
Of course I want to come
Not iron
But it dampened the Hong family's good intentions.
That's the head of the Hong family
Hong Li
I'm afraid that my good intentions won't be received
Instead, he compensated his daughter
But don't worry
My Hong family’s daughter-in-law
Still very tolerant
father
Don't waste your breath anymore
I don't have much time
Let's fight quickly
Your example 4 one
Who should I let go?
Your opponent is not me
Rather
he
Even if you have to find a scapegoat
Find a decent one too
Could this person be invited by the Han family from outside?
There must be no one available in the Han family.
It is impossible for the Han family to compete in such an important competition
Just find a scapegoat
Does the Han family think that this young man can't stand up to Chen'er?
Elder Yun
Can Chen'er defeat him?
I have the fighting skills of Fenglei Pavilion
The one who can defeat him among his peers
There may be some in Zhongzhou
But it hasn’t appeared in Tianbeicheng yet
Since Elder Yun has said so,
I want to see this guy after he loses
How ugly will the expression on Han Chi’s face be?
son
Give your name
nobody
Xiao Yan
Not as famous as Master Hong Chen
The Han family actually sent an unknown person to compete with me.
/ 'son
I'll give you ten breaths to think about it.
It's up to you to get out
Or should I waste it and throw it out?
No more ten breaths
Let’s do it directly
Since you are seeking death yourself
Then don't blame me
Is the thunder attribute fighting spirit?
son
Can be defeated by me
It's also your glory
Master Hong Chen
Such a little trick
Don't take it out
Thunderclaw
But that's it
Baji collapse
This little bit of lightning power
Want to hurt me too
You are actually the Seven-Star Fighting Emperor too
It turned out to be Dou Huang
No wonder the Han family wants to send him on the field
This level of strength is probably stronger than Han Yue's
Where does this kid come from?
This strength
Not like a nobody
But why have I never heard the name Xiao Yan in Zhongzhou Continent?
Zhongzhou Continent is extremely vast
Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon I don’t know how many people there are
It’s normal not to know
It's not that easy to win against me
Why not give up your wishful thinking
son
You asked for this
Today I will show you the secret method of Fenglei Pavilion
thunder god coming
Strength has skyrocketed
This momentum far exceeds that of the Seven Stars Dou Huang
His current strength
Almost reached the level of Nine Star Dou Huang
This Hong Chen, whether it’s martial arts, fighting skills or weapons
It's so powerful
No wonder he dares to be so arrogant
"degree." technique
Can force Chen'er to use secret techniques
That guy is really amazing
but
That’s it for now
/ \son
Keep your eyes open and see
Three thousand thunders
Came just in time
you are too slow
How could he keep up with the speed of three thousand thunders?
Secret time is limited
Not suitable for prolonged fighting
Thousand Shattering Thunder Hammer
Liuhe swimming ruler
It depends on how you block it
The power of mere wind and thunder
What's so arrogant about it?
flame points
Wave Devouring Ruler
This is your method
I really think highly of you
If you only have these means
Then what's next
Just let me do it instead
The Three Mysterious Transformations of Heavenly Fire and the Glazed Transformation
This is
strange fire
Where did this kid come from?
It's hidden so deeply
Is this the barrier above the peak of Dou Huang?
If I practiced the last two transformations of the Three Mysterious Transformations of Heavenly Fire
And match it with different fires
Maybe we can break through this barrier
this time
Chen'er is afraid something is wrong
This bastard
He actually hides his strength
What a powerful secret
Xue Diao I really invited an incredible god to my Han family.
while in college
He used the power of fighting spirit to face the fighting emperor.
Now several years have passed
Achievements are naturally more terrifying
That Hong Chen was in front of Xiao Yan
I can only admit defeat
But now
I need to deal with you first
I do not believe
Except for that monster Feng Qing'er
I will lose to anyone
Get up
This palm
I can't take your life
can force me into such a situation
Xiao Yan
you are the first
Such a shame and humiliation
Even if I lose my life today, I will make you pay the price
Thunder hammer
die to me
It seems you only have so much ability.
Then take my last move
Liuhe Youshenchi cracking fire
I surrender
he really won
this young man
It's really amazing
hateful
How could I lose to a nobody like you?
go to hell
Xiao Yan be careful
Three thousand thunders
stop