Subtitle by [www.gogoanime21.eu.org], thank you for faithfully watching at "[www.gogoanime21.eu.org]"
Su Yan and the Little Medical Fairy Zi Yan and Xin Lan are on their way to Zhongzhou through the space wormhole
Encountered a space storm attack
Facing the space storm that only the strong Dou Zun can escape
Xiao Yan, who was unwilling to give up, escaped from the space ship and was protected by
All parties safely send their companions out of the space wormhole
But he himself was swallowed by the weak spring of space
Xiao Yan, who had escaped the power of space, was accidentally teleported to the northern region of Zhongzhou.
dagger
Fortunately, he was rescued by Han Xue who returned to Tianbeicheng from the bandit team.
In order to repay Han Xue for saving her life
Xiao Yan hid his identity and blocked the road to rob the Han family's motorcade, Xia buried the monster
At this time Xiao, Yan and Zhenkou are dawning
He has a close relationship with the Han family
In my Han family, it is not the custom for two girls to serve one husband.
Your Hong family’s ridiculous request
My Han family will never agree
Hanbogo
You may not know yet
My nephew a few days ago
He has officially become a cabinet disciple of Fenglei Beige.
How could this be?
Uncle Han
My Hong family is no longer the same as before.
There must be no more suitable son-in-law candidate than me in Tianbeicheng.
You say
Is it right
No matter what your Hong family’s status is in Tianbei City in the future,
None of my daughters from the Han family will marry the Hong family.
Uncle Han
I have sent two elders to invite Han Xue
This is
The power of space
It seems that it was left in the body when it was destroyed by the force of space in the space channel.
Mr. Xiao Yan
drink some water
Fortunately, there was that mysterious senior who helped me.
otherwise
I'm afraid everyone has been buried in Wanshe Gorge
thank you
Oh no need
You keep it
It's strange to say
Usually if you don’t know each other
Few people care about such nosy matters
There are still many good people in this world
Just like Miss Han and I have never met but I saved me
correct
How is your recovery from your injury going?
A lot of things happened along the way
I forgot to care about you more
Come to Zhongzhou alone
It must not be easy along the way.
I came to Zhongzhou to travel with my friends
Unexpectedly encountered danger in a space wormhole
Fortunately, Miss Han rescued her
I am very grateful
His internal injuries were really serious
That senior should not be pretending to be him
There is no need to attack Xia, so polite
Your internal injuries are serious
Support as much as possible
Thank you, Ms. Han, for your concern.
This is no serious injury
Xinxin
There is an ambush
Someone ambushed the convoy
what happened
Hurry up
Protect supplies quickly
country
Go to the back quickly
thank you miss
It's the Hong family
Miss Han Xue
Our head of the Hong family invites you
Please come with us
You are dreaming
Miss
Are you okay?
Sure enough it's you
Xiao Yan Brothers
It's that mysterious strong man
Let’s solve these two problems first.
Your Excellency is born very well
It must be the first time to come to Tianbeicheng.
Take your people and get out
You must have never heard of the Hong family, right?
head
Offended the Hong family in Tianbeicheng
roll
arrogant boy
Do you think you defeated me with a sneak attack?
He can beat the two of me
You guys take a break
I'll take care of them
This guy
How dare you be so arrogant
Take action
Xuanhuo moves
woody
What is this
Looks like I'm going to die here today
Good fighting spirit fusion skills
It's just a pity
Fire has no use for me
This person is too strong
retreat
Now that we've started
Naturally, we can’t leave easily
Let you deal with them
Thank you Mr. Xiao Yan for your help.
Minpi fish
Less than three rounds
You can directly capture two four-star fighting emperors alive.
Look at our Han family
It’s hard to find a few people with such strength
whole team
Rush back to the Han family immediately
yes
Even if the Han sisters don’t marry, they have to marry
You Hong family, don’t go too far.
Hong Chen
If you dare to touch my sister
I will definitely let you die badly
Uncle Han
If something happens to you
After a while Han Xue came
It’s not easy for me to explain.
father sister
I'm back
Cher
You're not hurt, are you?
Senior Han Yue
This fate is so wonderful, right?
These two old guys
Can't even catch a fighting king
It's really embarrassing
Uncle Han
I'm done with this kiss
If you, the Han family, don’t know how to praise,
Don't blame our Hong family for using force.
I can give the Han family a way
As long as one of your Han family peers can defeat me
I, the Hong family, will never cause trouble to you again within ten years.
When iron
If defeated
Then Han Yue and Han Xue are all mine.
The Han family and even the entire Tianbei City
It is difficult for anyone of his generation to rival him
This competition
Just to bully me, there is no one in the Han family
But if Fenglei Beige intervenes in this dispute,
This contest
Our Han family is next
But if you lose
I marry you
But not my sister
According to your
It’s okay to marry your sister first
Sister, just wait a moment
Sister, I never agree
Do the participants in the war have to be from the Han family?
Xiao Yan
Senior Han Yue
Long time no see
Stay safe
Jie Fei
Do you know Mr. Xiao Yan?
who is this
This is my junior student at Canaan College
Xiao Yan
You can ask for foreign aid
I, Hong Chen, am not afraid of these things
Three are diseases
That being the case
Then Hong said goodbye today.
three days later
See you on Tianshi stage
It's so boring here
Walk
Why did you come to Tianbeicheng?
I heard that Zhongzhou Dan Pagoda will hold a Dan conference soon.
Let me see you
I see
Xiao Yan is a student of the inner courtyard like me.
He is still at the top of the inner court rankings
as far as I know
Can become the first in the inner courtyard of Canaan College
Little brother is really a dragon and a phoenix among men.
This is my father
He is also the head of the Han family
Uncle Han
Too much praise
Yue'er
The fight between you and Hong Chen in three days
Can be sure
I'm afraid it will be difficult to defeat Hong Chen with my strength.
but besides that
There is no other way
among peers
There are only a few people who can advance to the level of fighting stars.
Think of it as repaying Han Xue for saving her life.
And the friendship with senior Han Yue, right?
Why don't you let me come?
you
But your injury hasn't healed yet
Do not worry
Can be restored in a short time
Xiao Yan
Willing to fight on behalf of the Han family
This kid really has the strength to defeat Hong Chen
I'm tired of seeing it
It’s not that I don’t believe little brother Xiao Yan
Just that Hong Chen
Look at the entire Tianbei City
It is rare to find an opponent among peers
I have full confidence in Mr. Xiao Yan,
I hope he can represent our Han family in the battle
Cher
you sure
Father
I believe in Mr. Xi Yan’s ability
I have witnessed this journey with my own eyes
He forced Xia Mang back with just one move.
Even within three rounds
one against two
Captured Hong Mu Honglie alive
I know Xiao Yan
I think Xiao Yan is qualified to represent our Han family in the war.
Your vision is believed by the father
Capture Hongmu and his two men alive
Hong Chen can do it too
Besides, this kind of competition between swords and swords has no eyesight.
What if little brother Xiao Yan had any accidents happen to my Han family?
I can't feel sorry
Father
You don’t believe that Mr. Xiao Yan can defeat Hong Chen
Yue'er Xue'er
Since you have great confidence in this little brother Xiao Yan,
Then let uncle try it first
After all, this matter is related to the survival of the Han family.
There can be no negligence at all
Uncle, you
Then please enlighten me
If the kid is hit once by senior within ten rounds,
Even if I am not strong enough
willing to admit defeat
It seems that little brother Xiao Yan is very confident in himself.
This guy is really arrogant
Han Tian is the Eight-Star Fighting Emperor
Not on par with Hong Chen
yes
I'm afraid this guy will suffer a loss if he underestimates the enemy so much.
Do not worry〉
I think although my uncle is tempted,
But more importantly, I want to use facts to justify his name.
Little brother Xiao Yan
You have to be careful
My nine-turn wind wanders
But my Chengming skill
Five turns
This guy is very strong
Even if the second brother faces him life and death
I'm afraid he's not a match either.
I'm afraid this person can really compete with Hong Chen
Nine turns
The power of space
Over there
You are Douzong
It's just a coincidence
A trace of space power that I just barely mastered
Senior Han Tian
Accepted
Xiao Yan, little brother, you can control the power of space at the Douhuang level.
What a terrible future life!
I lost this contest
Little brother Xiao Yan
If our Han family can survive this crisis
Your kindness is unforgettable
I, Han Chi, am willing to pay all the costs