Light shines through the window at night
And look at the inch finger showing the silk dress
I look forward to the wine, but it is desolate
The bell rings and asks about the turbid wine in the world
A pot of broken heart
In the world
What's wrong with loving mediocrity?
When will the cold-eyed peach blossoms bloom?
Play Xiuxian Wonderful
Don't move God
The artistic conception of a monk lies within his magical powers
Experience it well
I Ching
This is the Yijing
Things change
The love is broken and it is heartless
Happy in my heart
Bullying the outside world is a mediocre pleasure
But what is my age?
Go to hell
My son
What's wrong
master
My destiny was broken
Please avenge me, Master.
What's going on?
Details
A thief escaped from the Shizi Mansion
The disciple was worried about the possibility of failure so he chased after him.
Who knew he was actually an accomplice?
He used the knife as a shield to injure his disciples.
If Fu Er hadn't run away desperately,
I'm afraid Master won't be able to see Fu'er anymore.
You can be sure
You just saw this person
There is no spiritual power in the body
It seems like the same as ordinary people.
Absolutely correct
Otherwise, why would I think he was a mortal?
Lead the way.
No need to test the horse
We're walking
I haven't taken a walk with you for a long time.
Farewell Master
Master really dotes on me.
From childhood to adulthood
He got into any trouble
The master will immediately help him out.
I haven't refused once in all these years.
Why
With the wisdom of the master
How can I not hear
There is a lot of untruth in what my junior brother said.
I don't know who has offended my junior brother this time.
Which sect are you from?
Easily broke the younger brother's natal Rakshasa
I see this person
It is likely to be an order.
Your master's position in the Four Sects Alliance
Don't say it's the Dan stage
Even in the Nascent Soul stage
The same outcome
withdraw
Dare to mess with me
I will make sure you die without a burial place
Sugar Man
Sugar man
How do you sell this candy man?
One copper coin
My Buddha is born in the year of the monkey.
Naturally I'd choose this one.
Do you like it?
Um
When I first saw you
You are fighting with a group of kids for a candy man
Maybe you have forgotten
How could I forget
Father and son are born with a hard life
If it weren't for the master, he would have died by now.
Let's go
Take me to see that person.
Speak
What's going on?
Blame it on the rain top
What rain top
The prince accidentally found a treasure
Name Yu Ding
The alliance has regulations
Civilian protection
Must be submitted
The prince was bewitched by the traitor
I was careless for a moment and secretly hid the
Who knew that he was discovered by Zhou Wutai of Baiyun Sect?
Directly ordered to kill the prince
The Political and Aide-de-camp
Now even if the prince offers himself
There is no escape from death
Over the years, the monks who have been replaced have retreated one by one.
I have no other choice
I had no choice but to run to Mr. Wang for help.
Save your life
The cause and effect of these 16 years of service have come to an end.
You go
Great Grace
Xu Tao keeps it in mind
return
We have guests
He is the master
He hurt me.
Taoist
How about letting me have a drink too?
Why
Good wine
Since you like
The remaining half pot is for you.
Hahaha
Your realm is one level higher than mine.
Transformed into a mortal
admire
Taoist friends share the words of disciples
Understanding the Way of Heaven through One Master and One Father
It has the same effect as mine
Why envy others?
Um
Today I listen to my disciple's words
Only then did I know that in Kyoto
There is someone who is at the same level as me and is ready to become a god
Why don't you and I compare ourselves?
See who enters the ethereal realm of incarnation first
how
With a comparative mind
I'm afraid Wang will never have another incarnation in this life.
My friend, your words are really harmful.
Hahahahahaha
I didn't expect that in Kyoto
It's a pleasure to meet such a fellow Taoist.
Next week Wutai
I don't know what to call you
Undead King Daoyou
Within a hundred years
You can definitely become a god
Zhou congratulates today
Another appointment with Mars
If you really hear
A hundred-year curse in my heart
If I cannot incarnate within a hundred years
Unless you realize it again
I'm afraid I'll never have the chance in this lifetime
It's too early for Zhou Daoyou to speak
In Wang's opinion
Within a hundred years
Whether Zhou Daoyou can enter the state of transformation is still a good question.
But your disciple will surely die within a hundred years.
Mr. Wang's words are sharp
If I make Zhou Wutai angry
But what can I do?
Could it be that he saw that Fu Er and I
The Key Points of One Teacher, One Father
This person's complex state
Through the understanding of the relationship between master and disciple
Motivation
Raising children with love
To show favor
Love with Heart
One cup of water
Every move
All to make him himself
Immerse yourself in this career
And he finally realized the meaning
There will be his incarnation
It was the time to kill his own disciple.
Killing the disciple whom he had placed all his heart and soul in
Makes him feel infinitely sad
The last step of being in a state of ecstasy
This god's artistic conception seems to be sentimental
In fact, ruthless
But this ruthlessness contains the utmost love and nature
First, make a hundred-year promise
Then it brought out the true ruthlessness in my heart
Sad obsession with the future
At the same time, in Foer's heart
Leaving a trace
He saw through me
I still don't know what he meant.
clever
Tell your Highness
Send Yu Ding to the Taoist temple within three days
I will not pursue this matter any further.
master
Your disciple will die within a hundred years.
Fu 2 Don't think too much
Why doesn't Tang Ren eat?
The disciple sent by the master intends to keep him forever
This person is my strongest enemy in my life.
This Mr. Wang is so powerful
The monk of Baiyun Sect
Obviously forced the other immortals to retreat
The prince was forced to hide in the palace and dare not go out
He made the immortal give up the pursuit with just a few words.
Desperate situation
A place of comfort
Still the Realm of Time
My mood
What will it be?
ah
Ahhh
Shopkeeper Wang
Chief Wang
daughter
Zeng, a man from Wei Wang, met the Wang brothers
Hey bro
I'm sorry.
How much is this
Hey, brother, if you don't mind
Come and have a meal
Ahhh
ah
You are not a religious person
Can only enter reincarnation
This flower can help you gaze into the soul
Then you can have a good body
grandfather
Where is this
In this abandoned cultivation heart
I actually had such a profound understanding.
However, with your mere Yuanying cultivation
Don't be too greedy
This kind of heaven has not lasted for millions of years.
Unable to find the origin
By then your body will have decayed.
Destined to die
Old Man Tianyunzi
Let’s make a good relationship today
If you can get out of this abandoned planet
Can you come to heaven to sit on my sacrifice
tomorrow
Follow the century
Go back
If it weren't for Senior Tianyunzi destroying my divine consciousness
I may get lost in the mysterious cycle of reincarnation
In the Way of Heaven
A hundred deaths finally solved
These years
It is nothing more than an imitation of the cycle of heaven and earth.
Not a real reincarnation
I still need to pursue my own opinion
Transformation
I am the undead
Determined to win
The days on earth always pass quickly
The blacksmith shop of the Daniu couple
It annexed three surrounding shops.
Business is booming
The bull also violated the ancestral teachings
Passed the blacksmithing skills to more gold
I don't want to iron.
I want to learn wood carving from Grandpa Wang
I don't even understand how to swing a hammer
Still want to do your grandpa Wang's delicate work
You ignorant little bastard.
Ah, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts
Wang Shuo
I won't bring you wine today.
I can't drink it every day when I'm old.
Go Slow
Obviously you are here
Children come here
Root bone Qijia
Best place for spiritual practice
How about letting me accept him as my disciple?
Of course
It doesn't matter if Xiao Niu doesn't practice well.
Come back steadily
Wow it's snowing
Over
Why did it snow so early this year?
Summer is coming soon
Okay, stop playing.
This blood
There is murderous intent
Even if there is thunder, I will also hit the snowman
There is a mechanism to conceal
I rely on