A dream of ten thousand years
He plays the eighty-year-old
Later you coil
In my territory
It's not your turn to stir up trouble here.
Whether it is a demon or a Buddha
Get down on your knees.
Chief Han Yue
If you obey me
I can protect the lives of your entire family.
Come
Be happy, beauty is not yours
Don't stretch your dog's paws
I'm going to kill you today, run away
Too late
The Lord has taken care of it.
No one from the two halls of Zhengyang Sect escaped
Ye Chen, when did you become the Holy Lord of Yanhuang?
More than that
I am still the Xingyue Sect Leader.
Zhengyang Sect has always been ambitious
In order to unify Lanchu
Secretly provoked many bloody storms
I used all my strength to stop the Zhengyang Sect.
Fellow Taoist Pan Yue
I wonder if the Shangguan family is willing to join
this
If you can join
I can help you
The people of Lingxu Realm opened up the Danhai and Shenhai
The Danhai that only Kongming Realm possesses
The spiritual realm can also be opened up
Try it and you'll know
The Shangguan family wishes to respect the industry leader
Send
May the Lord send
My Shenhai and Danhai are competing with each other
Thank you so much, Ye Chen
Sorry I
I can compete with the sea of ​​elixir and the sea of ​​spirit at once
You are also talented.
I'm just the icing on the cake
I have something else to do so I'm leaving first
Wait a minute
ah
The mountain
You get up first.
If I hadn't eaten you that day in Luan Gu Cang Yuan, you wouldn't have died.
Do you know how happy I am?
Ye Chen
I want to be your bride
It's no use telling me this.
You have to get out of here.
I'm not going to say it's not done yet.
Opening up a new approach to the single sea
escape
ah
Ye Chen is too much
Shangguan Yuer
You are a dog and you bite people.
Why
What is this called?
This is
Colorful exquisite flowers
One of the rarest materials for refining elixirs
I didn't expect to see it here.
Hey
Feels really good
Ahhh
ah
Fellow Daoist Hanyue
What a coincidence!
Just now you are
What is the situation
I am the body of the sword spirit
In the early years, I captured the colorful exquisite flower queen
Sometimes it has a strange fragrance like other flowers.
Isn't it true that the blood has the effects of this flower?
If used to make alchemy
Fellow Daoist Hanyue
Can you give me
Have a baby
ah
Shameless Old Dragon
What shameless!
I'm helping you.
Well
Daoist Ye Chen not only saved the Shangguan family's life,
His strength and character are also excellent
He is indeed the best candidate for a husband.
I accepted your proposal.
Ye Chen
You're such a playboy
Young people, please exercise moderation.
Otherwise, what will I do when I get old?
go
Where are your Yin Cang and Pang Tong?
The Holy Lord has commanded
Zhengyang Sect has two soul jade tablets
Killing him might alert the enemy.
So it's just for their cultivation.
Zhengyang Sect and Qingyun Sect form an alliance
Plan to join forces to divide the Hengye clan
Oh no! The Qingyun Sect is attacking the Xiong family in southern Xinjiang.
Go fast to save people
Uh-huh
The ending cannot be broken
Even if I die, I will be satisfied
Bear, you can't die.
I
The heart and soul were seriously injured and could not be saved.
Don't waste it
It's chilly
What discouraging words
This old guy always says that good people don't live long
I
I advise you
It seems that I am a good person.
How can you be a good person when you are full of bad intentions?
Stop making trouble
Make no mistake
Keep your word
Wow
Why is the answer still open?
The most running
Do you want to protect Danhai?
I'll take care of the rest.
Brother Long San
It's my brother who has implicated you.
I still don't understand the reason why the King of Chu is so cold
It's a pity that the younger generation didn't escape
It seems that there is no need to go to Xishu Private School again.
The whole army
ah
Evil Minister
Lightning Lightning
Qingyun Sword, Absolute Sword, and Shield
Ye Chen, I, Qingyun Sect, don't have time to look for you.
You come to the door quickly
court death
I've heard similar things before.
You don't need to worry about it.
He is the Nomura mentioned by the second kid.
He, a Kunlun sword, actually
Seven Kinds of Heroes
We go to help
ah
You can't go anywhere except to the underworld.
I am not familiar with Huangquan Road.
Or you lead the way?
Free Turn
I'll give you one for this trip.
How could Lian Zhu's Yan Huang come here?
Why are people from Hengyuan here?
Sun Yunzong left no one behind
All Yanhuang members obey orders
kill
How did Yanhuang and Hengyue join forces?
Because Master Hengyue and Saint Yanhuang are both mine
Hey
It's all because I'm too talented.
So one person is both Liangzhu
Then I'll take you down first.
Let them be cautious
Qingyun Sword
Jian Luo Tian Wang
Ahhhh
You're a spirit craftsman
How is it possible to mobilize the spirits of heaven and earth?
Domination
Changes
Not good
Qingyun Sect
Destroy them all
kill
Famine
Godly Equipment
Peng Yue
It's all you
There's no way I can be so outstanding.
I will respect you if you dress up randomly, haha
Brother's Redemption
I'm so grateful, bro.
If you have anything to ask in the future, just let me know.
Big Brother, I will never give up
Ye Cheng and I are also brothers
You become my brother.
Hahaha
Go away
I won't say much about the polite words between Patriarch Xiong and Patriarch Situ.
I want both of you to join Hengyue
I don't know if
Dad, do you agree?
Yue Zun not only cured my injury
And I opened up the Danhai
I don't agree to it.
You opened up Danhai in Qujing
Unheard of
My Situ family also agreed.
With your two families' help
We will be more confident in dealing with the Zhengyang Sect.
And this time, the revenge of Qingyun Sect
Who is there
The first Qingyun Sect ship captured
I didn't expect there was still a fish that slipped through the net of Qingyun Sect.
Keep someone
This time, Qingyun Sect attacked Xiong Family
It is the letter from Zhou Aolai that he was domestically abused by his private disciples
Thanks to him, the Situ family arrived in time.
Let's resist Qingyun together
My Xiong family can hold out until you guys come.
ah
Why do you do this?
Lu Hou killed my beloved
woman
You killed him
Avenged me
You are my benefactor
Great favor cannot be repaid
I am willing to help you take down Qingyun Sect
I have a way to get rid of the Wudang Patriarch
How dare someone deliberately frame me?
I want to see who is so bold.
Who dares to pretend to be me?
Get out of this seat
Calm down in the clouds
Someone is deliberately framing this sect.
Today, my Zhengyang Sect will fight your Qingyun Sect to the death.
The little witch seems to be controlled
Calculation
Shy words
Bloody as first sight