Subtitle by [www.gogoanime21.eu.org], thank you for faithfully watching at "[www.gogoanime21.eu.org]"
I never bend my knees in my life
Oh, look, look
Hear the pressure on the ancient altar on the fourth floor
Like carrying a mountain on one's back
He can still move forward quickly
I don't know how he did it.
It seems that climbing to the top of this ancient altar is an experience in itself.
To seal the bomb, only for the divine liquid
Since ancient times
Those who ascend to the ninth level of the altar
Everyone can rule the world
You can leave your name on the magnificent monument
Be famous forever
Leave your name quickly
Now you can know who this person is.
Ah, how audacious
He actually left such a word
How bold
What does this mean?
In what manner
That's outrageous
Remember
This word is not humiliation, but glory, achievement, and brilliance.
Sooner or later the truth will be revealed to the world
That's right, that's great. That's right.
He can still move forward
I will take the Supreme Liquid
The soul transforms into a holy fetus again
This supreme liquid contains the avenue of gods
When the divine fire is lit
It will definitely help me understand more
Where did the sin and blood show up?
So strong
If you were put into the immortal ancient ruins
I'm afraid that it will be given to the disciples of various ancient religions.
Bring big trouble
Three God-level magic weapons
If the disciple can't defeat him, will God take action?
They are all treasures that can completely obliterate the true soul.
It seems that they are planning to kill me here.
It's a pity that this is the spiritual world
Anyone comes to you
We can only use the realm of venerable people
And in the realm of the venerable
i am invincible
I came but still want to leave
Bloody crime
You killed the disciples of the great sect indiscriminately
Fight against divine punishment
break the rules
Will be suppressed today
I passed the spiritual test
You are waiting but trying to do harm
It’s fair to say that I broke the rules
This thing is the most precious treasure of ancient religions
You can break through the shackles of the Venerable Realm here
You should die
Break through the shackles
When I was a teenager, I was able to break through the shackles of my realm.
You dare to hurt me
There is no place for you in Sin State anymore
Humph, you never intended to give me a place to stay.
three
shellfish
you you
your biggest mistake
You shouldn't mess with me
Ahhh this
great uncle
gods
He killed the god
The leader of the Kuai Kuai Kou
God died
Assessment ends
Ten thousand venerables can leave the spiritual world
Carrying the body into an uninhabited country
This is where the leader comes in
Bin Hui accidentally died in the no man's land
Three Coins Meifu Two, Qianzhou
Fifty million Venerable Realm monks passing through customs
Country by state
Welcome to the blooming fairy flowers
Entering Immortal Ancient
Very strong wave carrier
A group of common people who have never seen the world
Immortal flower buds are about to appear
Nature will bring auspiciousness and good fortune
otherwise
Let our group of venerables
Going into no man's land to die in vain?
Just this light and rain coming
It can extend people’s life span by a hundred years
Xiandaohua lives up to its name
Three thousand petals, three thousand states
"1/ Major apricot religions
Major ancient religions
Can observe with mana
The situation of Sizi in the Immortal Ancient Relics
Able to observe the condition of part C from the outside
That being the case
It seems there is no need to hide my identity any longer.
You are pretty good
Why don't you follow me?
Tianyao Ge, Qian
It's better than entering Immortal Ancient and giving away your "life"
celestial demon
If you are in the realm of Venerables, you dare to name yourself Heaven
It seems that you are quite capable
That's natural
It is your glory to follow me
It's a pity that I'm alone
Does not include groups
Don't know how to praise
larvae
Ying Yinglong
Yinglong
It must have been attracted by these immortal flower buds
Lu Ya
Ambergris crystals
Good fortune from heaven
These ambergris crystals belong to my heavenly demon Ge Qian.
Who contends with
Not ambergris
It's a dragon
What a heavenly demon who has seen the world.
The competition for geniuses in the Three Thousand States finally begins
See who is respected in this life
No wonder it is called fairy flower.
Each petal represents a kind of avenue
Mapping the past and present
Those sages could not suppress it
Instigated to ignite the divine fire
It should be a place of opportunity
But it became a burial place
Those giant petals are occupied by major ancient religions
Although it is difficult for us casual cultivators to compete
But there is always a path for you and me on the Three Thousand Avenues
These small flaps are the gateway for you and me to enter the ancient world.