I
My trauma
Dark Night
ah
silence
If summarized
Like Chinese characters moving forward
Sabertooth Field Sword
Thunder Dragon Hand
Xiao Ji came here to join the Tang Sect
You made him feel at home.
Master Xuan, we have unanimously decided to fight on behalf of the Tang Sect
Um
Let me try your soul contract.
But I've already given you my soul ring.
No hope
Wait, this is my second soul.
Tianmeng Ice Silkworm
Wait a minute.
Dong'er, what's wrong with you?
Strangely, there is nothing wrong with his body.
Is there something wrong with the sea of ​​spirit?
Could it be
Teacher Yelangesang said
The shadow in Wang Dong's spiritual sea is a magical stone
If the problem is there
I'm afraid that Xuan Lao and the others are powerless.
My second uncle said it was left by my father.
Let me give you
It has my father's seal on it.
Cannot be disassembled directly
Said to wait for the opportunity
Could it be that Niu Bo Taibo had anticipated this?
ah
There is a spiritual seal
This seal is very delicate.
But with your current mental strength, you can break it.
You are too impatient
The mental coordination is too chaotic
Calm down
Run again
Watch me break him
Um
It's a letter
Yu Hao
When you see this letter
I believe Xiaodong's body has already shown abnormality.
I believe you already know
There is a seal in Xiaodong's spiritual sea
This seal
It was set up by Xiaolong's parents with great difficulty.
To protect his spirit
Xiaodong's identity is very unusual
He told you
His soul ring
Need to go to the Haotian Sect's forbidden area, Shengtian Pavilion to obtain
To be exact, it is to retrieve
Each of his soul rings
All of these are beyond his current limit.
That's why his parents tried their best
Set a seal in his spiritual sea
No wonder
Dong'er's second soul ring is the purple thousand-year soul ring
Xiaodong sealed it when he obtained the fifth soul ring
There is looseness
We can't strengthen the seal.
But there is a way to consolidate Xiaodong's own
Greatly improve the body's endurance
so
The danger when he absorbs the spirit ring will be greatly reduced.
This method requires fresh herbs
Because of the love heartbreak red
This fairy grass is located in the Sunset Forest of the Sky Soul Empire
A treasure land called Yin Yang Eyes of Ice and Fire
Huo Yuhao
It's you, Wang Qiuer
I have to leave town urgently.
What do you want?
I'll tell you when I come back.
Where are you going out of town?
Just don't worry about it.
That place is dangerous.
Tell me not to care
You don't make it clear
Do I still have to care?
Huo Yuhao
Wang Qiuer, stop me again
Don't blame me for not caring about my friendship
What is it?
Why did your face change?
Save people
Is it Wang Donger?
Sure enough, I thought about it.
It seems that only he is worthy of you doing this
I share the hardships with Dong'er
Not loyal
His safety
It was I, Huo Yuhao, who risked everything for the
But all my friends
All the people who are important to me
It's worth my risk.
Who is up there?
Looks like a student of Shrek Academy
Wang Qiuer, if you are in danger
I will make the same choice
Wait, I'll go with you.
Didn't you say I'm your friend too?
good
The seal of the big brother's bag has been unlocked
Yuhao this kid
The growth rate is faster than we expected
But with his current cultivation
Is it too dangerous to go to that place?
Once the arrow is shot, there is no turning back
Since Huo Yuhao has unlocked the secret bag
It means taking the test
Besides, Xiaodong's problem
It is indeed only he who can solve
ah
I've been flying all night.
Huo Yuhao, where is our destination?
Sky Soul Empire
well
Where is the junior brother at this time?
Just now, the Shrek City Defense Guard sent a message
The monitor was out of town last night.
With him
There is another person leaving the city
Wang Qiuer
We are almost entering the Tianhun Empire.
Is it the Sky Soul Empire's airspace guard?
The person in front
You have entered the Tianhun Empire
Please land immediately
Accept identity verification
Mu Xue turns out he is from the Heavenly Soul Empire
My name is Weiner
These three are
Mo Feiyun
Mu Xue and Bei Tang
I'll deal with them.
Don't be dissatisfied with life
Accept the fight
Very strong mental strength
Don't be blind
I have the key
You stop blocking me.
Don't blame me for not remembering the past
Star Forest Team
Could it be him?
Captain, should we notify the outpost ahead?
No need for Zujie
That was a friend who helped us.
Sunset Forest has arrived
The destination is in the heart of the forest
Have you noticed that the sky seems to be getting darker?
What's going on?
Is this dust?
No, it's not toxic, it's flatulence
etc.
Bauhinia Devil Child's Spiritual Detection
Detection
Such a thick miasma
We are only at the outskirts of the forest.
Shortness of breath
If you go deep into the forest, you will definitely be poisoned to death.
Although the ultimate weapon is the nemesis of all poisons
But the miasma is so large
My soul can't stand it
Maybe there is a risky way to try
The danger here is far beyond our expectations.
Wang Qiuer, are you sure you won't go?
What about you?
I have tried
Thinking about losing him
What will happen to me?
I found that my world would turn gray
In my heart, there is no life
Even life is hopeless
That’s when I was surprised to find
In my heart
His life is more important than my own.
You are such a hopeless idiot.
But I can't bear to see a fool die.
good
High-explosive incendiary bomb
Launch Launch
Ask God to detect
Shared steps
I saw that it was the center of the forest.
Hold on to Wang Qiuer
We take turns using Soul Island to push
The engine accelerates at full speed
Should be able to break out of this poison stick
Although miasma can be ignited
But the miasma here is too dense
The burned part will be filled soon.
Soul Shield
It can protect us from the miasma temporarily.
The toxicity of the battle flag is too strong
The Minister can't stop it.
Brave Fighter
We're halfway through the day.
Substitution
That's an extremely rare poison.
Plant-type soul beasts are on the verge of becoming seven dead
They are the source of the miasma.
Passing through the colorful sea of ​​flowers
It's the destination.
The consumption of our soul power has reached the limit.
The only chance
It's a bet on the wolf ape's soul bone.
Maybe there is a risky way to try
Risky approach
You absorb this first.
This is the wolf ape's soul bone
If we are friends, don't hesitate.
Absorbed quickly
good
Thanks
Three-life energy left push protection skill
Watermark
Did it succeed?
Here is
Yin-Yang Eyes
A pot of cold water
Half Extremely Hot
Half is extremely cold
Ice and Fire
Twins at first sight
Cold Yin Fist
Hot Yangquan
Complementary and counteractive
It is one of the three types of cornucopia stones.
But it's dangerous
Don't you feel
Because there is a strong breath of life here
Have most plants evolved into plant soul-sucking beasts?
real
Very hot spring water
ah
Banner Soldier
Dare to trespass
Ice and Fire
Able to speak human language
This Ganoderma has been cultivated for at least 100,000 years.
I am not a hundred thousand year old soul beast
However, because of the nourishment of the two years of ice and fire
One day of our growth is equivalent to ten days in the outside world
so
Although I am only 10,000 years old
But it can be equivalent to 100,000 years old
We have no ill intentions, seniors.
I just came to ask for a herb to save people.
Hum, you still want to rob things
Then I can't let you go.
Wang Qiuer, I will fight him in close combat, and you can attack from a distance.
ah
Emperor's Wrath
Hydropower
Golden Dragon Fist
Are you going
Soul sacrifice is invalid
That soul island can
This won't destroy him.
You pissed off the fire girl.
Enough of testing
His moves aren't very strong.
But the body temperature is too high
We can't fight at full strength.
I summoned Xuannv to suppress his temperature
Then we attack with all our might
Ah, it's hot
Falling into the herd
His blazing flame suddenly became
ah
I heard you want to win my heart
Scan this QR code now
Follow us on WeChat
Get exclusive information about the plot in advance
Let me tell you the secret to impressing me
Scan the QR code and we will be waiting for you on the official WeChat account
Just call me Youyou
If you dare to eat this herb
I believe you
If only I could save him
I'm willing to do anything
Life is in your eyes
Is it something that can be easily given up for others?
I didn't expect Yuhao to sacrifice his life for Dong'er.
Even if Huo Yuhao wakes up
You all have to let go when he dies.